nationalteammanager.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy policy - Online Soccer Manager

**Gamebasics** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Online Soccer Manager. 

We can be reached via e-mail at [info@onlinesoccermanager.com](mailto:info@onlinesoccermanager.com) if you have any questions regarding our policies outlined below. Please be aware that we cannot 100% guarantee these policies, although we do our very best to abide by the policies which we have outlined. 

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded. It is used to improve the content of our Web page, to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, and never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. 

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitor preferences and record past activity in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, and to ensure that visitors are not repeatedly presented with the same banner ads. 

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by using this form

Regarding Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have contacts within other companies that we allow to place ads on our web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. 

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at any time in the future, we will contact you and post the policy changes to our Web site before we use your data for these new purposes. This way you will be aware of the policy change and have the option to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by writing us at the above address. 

Upon request, we will provide site visitors with access to the information that we have collected and that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by writing to us at the above address. Consumers can have this information corrected this way as well. 

With respect to security: we do not collect online information from any of our visitors for intentions of redistribution. We solemnly guarantee that any information you submit to us will not be sold or bartered to any third parties, unless express consent is given by yourself to do so. 

As with many online agencies today, Online Soccer Manager tries its best to abide by the privacy policy guidelines as explained above. However, we cannot 100% guarantee our privacy policy to be accurate to a tee, as our advertisers or ISPs may from time to time change their privacy policies or legal disclaimers without any prior notification. If any such instance results in any damages being suffered, Online Soccer Manager and any subsidiaries of Online Soccer Manager have no legal liability for these damages.
